John W. Tukey Papers 1937-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.117
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Works By Tukey, 1938-1994; 25 linear feet
  - Subseries A. Papers, 14 linear feet
    - Management of Weather Resources, The, 1978; 1 item; Statistical Task Force to the Weather Modification Advisory Board
    - Maps, Maps, Maps, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Marrying Data Analysis to Graphics, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Matching Low Moments of Arbitrary Distributions with Finite Sets, 1967 May 2; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Mathematical and Intuitional Treatment of Variance in Three Dimensions, The, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Mathematical Consultants, Computational Mathematics and Mathematical Engineering, 1955; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Mathematical Science and its Application, 1967; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Mathematics and the Picturing of Data, 1974; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Mathematics and the Picturing of Data, 1974; 1 items; Tukey, John W
    - Mathematics, Applied Mathematics and Mathematical Engineering, 1965 November 28; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Mathematics, 1964; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Matrix Inversion, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Means and Deviations based on Distances Between Percentage Points of Frequency Curves, 1965; 1 item; Pearson, E. S. and John w. Tukey
    - Measurement of Power Spectra from the Point of View of Communications Engineering, The, n.d.; Folder 1; Blackman, R. B. and John W. Tukey
    - Measurement of Power Spectra from the Point of View of Communications Engineering, The, n.d.; Folder 2; Blackman, R. B. and John W. Tukey
    - Measurement, Adjustment, and the Census Undercount, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Measuring Noise Color - 1A. Planning Spectrum Experiments, 1949 December 15; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Measuring Noise Color 1, n.d.; 1 item; Hamming, R. W. and John W. Tukey
    - Mechanisms of Adjustment, 1991 may 29; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Median of the Minumum Deviation from the Median, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Memorandum on a Possible Graduate Program in Quantitative Methodology, 1963 January 3; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Memorandum on Statistics in the Federal Government - Part I and II, 1949; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Memorandum on Statistics in the Federal Government, 1949; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Methodological Comments Focused on Opportunities, 1980; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Methodology, and the Statistician's Responsibility for Both Accuracy and Relevance, 1976 January 23; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Methods for Direct and Indirect Graphic Display for Data Sets in 3 and More Dimensions, 1980; 1 item; Tukey, Paul A., and John W. Tukey
    - Mini-Computers and Statistics, 1976; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Missing Values in Factorial Arrays, Perhaps Usefully Robust, 1994; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Modern Factory Experimentation and Related Design Choices: Opportunities for Research, 1984; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Modern Statistical Techniques in Data Analysis, 1976 August 5; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Modern Techniques of Power Spectrum Estimation, 1967; 1 item; Bingham, Christopher, Michael D. Godfrey and John W. Tukey
    - Molecules Carried on Dresel Particles, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Moments of Random Group Size Distributions, 1940; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Monte Carlo Techniques in a Complex Problem about Normal Samples, n.d.; 2 items; Arnold, Harvey J., Bradley D. Bucher, Hale F. Trotter, and John W. Tukey
    - More Honest Foundations for Data Analysis, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - More on Q-Q Plots and Related Topics, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - More on Quadrature, 1982; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - More Principled View of the Control of Data-Modification Displays, A (January afterthoughts), 1983 January 9; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - More Rational Approach to Analyzing our 5x5x5 and Related Matters, Emphasizing Symmetry, 1982; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - More Realistic Techniques for Data Analysis, 1981; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - More Sensitive and Searching Inquiry into 'Field Bias,' A, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - More Trustworthy and Effective Data Analysis, 1985; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Multi-Action Approach Designed to Make Sideslip Effective, 1985; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Multiple Comparison for Education Data, 1994; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Multiple Comparisons Through Orderly Partitions: The Maximum Subrange Procedure, n.d.; 1 item; Braun, Henry I. And John W. Tukey
    - Multiple Comparisons, n.d.; Folder 1; Tukey, John W
    - Multiple Comparisons, n.d.; Folder 2; Tukey, John W
    - Multiplicity: Philosophy and Practice, 1999 March 8; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Multipliciy Introduction, 1976; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Multipresponse Pictures for Main Effect and Other Overlays, 1991 August 21; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Multivariate Analysis of Mineralogic, Lithologic, and Chemical Composition of Rock Bodies, 1956; 1 item; Krumbein, W. C. and John W. Tukey
    - Named and Faceless Values: An Initial Exploration, In Memory of Prasanta C. Mahalanobis, 1 item; Krumbein, W. C. and John W. Tukey
    - Naming Large and Small Parts, Tukey, John W
    - National Assessment of Educational Progress, A Project of the Education Commission of the States, Report 5. 1969-1970, 1971 April; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - National Assessment of Educational Progress, A Project of the Education Commission of the States, 1970 July; Folder 1; Tukey, John W
    - National Halothane Study, 1969; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - National Ocean Goals: 1959-1960, 1977 January 25; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Natural Sequences of Flexibility in Multivariable Unit Response Function Fitting, 1981 November 24; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Natural Variability of Vital Rates and Associated Statistics, 1986; 1 item; Breslow, N., C. L. Chiang, J. M. Hoem, P. Jagers, N. Keiding, L. Kish, K. G. Manton, and J. W. Tukey
    - Needs for Training, 1963; 6 items; Tukey, John W
    - Nested Designs, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - New Approaches to Automatic and Semiautomatic Indexing and a Citation Index for Statistical Methodology, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - New Parametrization for Plane of Pearson Curves, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - New Pip, 1964 February 16; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - New Techniques, 1952; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - New Tools for Shapes of Distribution, 1983 February 22; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Next Future of Data Analysis, The, 1989 July 3; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Ninther, A Technique for Low-effort Robust (Resistant) Location in Large Samples, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - NkNS Forests, 1977 November 23; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Noise Silencing Opportunities, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Non-Parametric Estimation. I. Validation of Order Statistics, 1945; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Non-Parametric Estimation. II. Statistically Equivalent Blocks and Tolerance Regions - The Continuance Case, 1947; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Non-Parametric Estimation. III. Statistically Equivalent Blocks and Tolerance Regions - The Discontinuance Case, 1948; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - NonLinear (Nonsuperposable) Methods for Smoothing Data, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Nonparametric Procedure for Comparing Multivariate Point Sets, A, n.d.; 1 item; Friedman, Jerome H., Sam Steppel, and John W. Tukey
    - Nonparametric Statistical Data Modeling, Comment on, 1979; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Nonparametric Sum of Ranks Procedure for Relative Spread in Unpaired Samples, 1957-58; 5 items; Siegal, Sidney and John W. Tukey
    - Nonuniqueness Theorum, A, 1949; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notch Plots for Counted Rates, 1977 January 12; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Note on Adjusted R2, 1992 January 2; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Note on Least Squares and Unbiased Estimates, A, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Note on Linear Functionals, A, 1938; 1 item; Boas, Ralph P., Jr. and John W. Tukey
    - Note on Monte Carlo Method for Computing Properties of a Random Sample Drawn from a Normal Distribution, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Note on Some X2 Normalizations, 1949 July 12; 1 item; Tukey, John W. and Charles P. Winsor
    - Note on Some X2 Normalizations, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Note on the Problem of the Nile, A, 1948 December 3; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Note on the Square-Root Iteration, 1948 November 2; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes for Panel Discussion of Gilliland Report, 24 February 1963, 1963 February 24; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Notes in a Series of Lectures by Dr. S. M. Ulam, 1937 Spring; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes in Mathematics (237-)238, Functional Analysis., 1936-1937; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes in Physics (211)-212, Modern Theories of Atomic Structure., 1937; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on a Class of (usually) Non-linear Boxes, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on Analytic Geometry of Vectors, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on Cancer Rates, 1977 January 22; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on Linear Fitting, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on Output from Reduction-Steered Regression Programs, 1963; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on Package Storage for Throw-Downs, 1962 April 10; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on Plans for Tail-Cropping, levels 4, 5, 6, 7, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on Quick and Denormalized Methods of Analyzing Data, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on the Analysis of "Immersed" Variance, 1954 August 9; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on the Mean Square Successive Differences as Squared Denominators, 1976; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on the Swindles for Location and Scale, 1993; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes on the Use of the Range in Industrial Statistics, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes Upon Certain of the Questions Proposed by the COSATI Panel on Information Sciences Technology, 1966 January 5; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Notes: Some Elementary Problems of Importance to Small Sample Practice, 1948 December; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Numerical Methods, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Old - New Automobile Data, The, n.d.; 1 item; Hoaglin, David C. and John W. Tukey
    - On a Methodological Question Arising in the Halothane Study, 1965 April 11; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - On Calculating Intrinsic Accuracies from % Points, 1972 July 29; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - on Chinch Bug Control, n.d.; 1 item; Moore, Peter G. and John W. Tukey
    - On Robustifying the Jackknife, n.d.; 1 item; Fernholz, Luisa T. and John W. Tukey
    - On the "Virtues" of 4253H (or 4253H, twice) for Short/Moderate Sequences, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - On the Comparative Anatomy of Transformations, [1957]; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - On the Distribution of the Fractional Part of a Statistical Variable, 1938; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - On Widthing, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - One Degree of Freedom for Non-Additivity, 1949; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - One Question is Better, 1970 June 4; 1 item; Lord, Frederic M. and John W. Tukey
    - One- and Two-Degree of Freedom Data Window Problem, The, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - One-and-a-Bit Tails is Often Enough!, 1989; 4 items; Tukey, John W
    - Open Letter to All Re-Analyzers, 1979 October 11; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Optimizing Functions of Aggregative Criteria, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Orderly Tool Kit, The, 1987 August 31; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Organization and Display of Data Analysis Operations in a General Purpose Data-Analysis System, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Organization and Display of Data Analysis Operations in a General Purpose Data-Analysis System, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Orthogonal Polynomials for Geographic Trends: A Synopsis, 1991 February 5; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Oscillating Stochastic Approximater, The, 1977 July 7; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Outline and Discussion of Multresponse Processess, 1977; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Outline of a Computation Program for Scoring Poisson Data, 1956; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Outline of an Algorithm for Robust Dendral Components, 1979 October 3; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Outline of the Development of the FFT in the 60's, 1992; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Outside Test for Association, The, n.d.; 3 items; Olmstead, Paul S. and John W. Tukey
    - Outstanding Opportunities for Further Work: Linear Models Fitted to Finite Data, 1971; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Over the Hill and Just Beyond the Horizon, 1967; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Overnight Experimental-Sampling System: Shell, 1992 February 5; 1 item; Tukey, Paul A., and John W. Tukey
    - Overview of Techniques of Data Analysis, Comments On, 1980; 4 items
    - Overview of Tehcniques of Data Analysis, Exphasizing its Exploratory Aspects, An, n.d.; 1 item; Mallows, Colin T. and John W. Tukey
    - Ozone Trend Detection as a "Fire Alarm", 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Panel on the Environment, [1969]; 5 items; President's Science Advisory Committee
    - Paper on Pollution, 1966 July 25; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Parallel Determination and Multiple Comparisons, Lecture II, Reminder Sheet, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Parallel Plot Attuned to Mean Squares, A, 1989 March 31; 1 item; Hoaglin, David C. and John W. Tukey
    - Partial and Multiple Statistics, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Path Analysis, n.d.; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Pattern of Age at Dealth for Resident Members of the American Philosophical Society, 1971 April 19; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Pattern-Recognition Problem: Curly Contrails in the Snow!, 1982 March; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Peaceful Uses of Ballistic Missiles, The, n.d.; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Percentage of the Range, 1989 February 6; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Percentage Points of the Studentized Maximum Modulus, n.d.; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Performance and Information in a Photint System, 1982; 1 item; McCallum, Philip H. and John W. Tukey
    - Performance of Some Resistant Rules for Outlier Labeling, 1986; 1 item; Hoaglin, David C., Boris Iglewicz, and John W. Tukey
    - Permuted (Circularly-Shifted) Indexes to Abbreviations: A Mechanically Prepared Aid to Serial Indentification, 1 item; Tompkins, Mary L. and John W. Tukey
    - Permuted Index to Minimum Abbreviations for About 2500 "Journals", 1964; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Philosophy and Details in the Determination of Smoothing Factors, 1990; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Philosophy of Multiple Comparisons, The, 1991; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Piecewise Linear MultiMedianPolish of the Data Set, 1995 June 13; 10 items; Morganthaler, Stephan, and John W. Tukey
    - Plausible Thoughts on "Browsing", n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Point Estimation of Location: Technical Choices, n.d.; 1 item; Morganthaler, Stephan, and John W. Tukey
    - Pollution on the Wild, n.d.; 1 item; Buckley, John L. and John W. Tukey
    - Polynomial Fitting Near the Ends of Equally Spaced Data; The Empirical Facts, 1974 July; 1 item; Montricher, Gilbert Mayor de and John W. Tukey
    - Polyranges and Natural Approximation, 1989 May 31; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Possibilities and Choices in the Search for Nonlinear Artifacts When the Appropriate Subspace in not the Whole Space or one Dimension Less then the Whole Space, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Possible Applications of Quartimax -- and (Possibly) Stepwise -- Approaches in Frequency Analysis, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Possible Contouring Package, A, 1966 January 22; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Possible Plan for Iteratively Fitting the major Behavior of Multiple Reponses to Many Variables, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Possible Structure of Chunking Subprograms, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Possible Structure of Chunking Subprograms, 1967; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Potential Boiler-Plate Re: Incomplete Beta, 1965 March; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Power in the Comparison of Responses or Ordered, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Power Spectral Methods of Analysis and Application in Airplane Dynamics, 1956; 1 item; Press, H. and John W. Tukey
    - Practical Applications of New Theory a Review Part I-IV, 1949-1950; 5 items; Mosteller, Frederick and John W. Tukey
    - Practical Regression, 1983; 1 items; Tukey, John W
    - Practical Relationship Between the Common Transformations of Percentages or Fractions and of Amounts, The, 1960 June; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Practicality of Utopia, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Practice of Fitting Initial Sections of Power Series, The, n.d.; 1 item; Beaton, Albert and John W. Tukey
    - Practice of Spectrum Analysis, The, 1981; Folder 1; Tukey, John W
    - Practice of Spectrum Analysis, The, 1981; Folder 2; Tukey, John W
    - Practicing Statistician Looks at the Transactions, A., 1966; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Precis of Guided Re-Expression, With Some Commentary, A, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Precis on the Jackknife, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Preliminary Draft of 16 February 1960, 1960 February 16; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Preliminary Tests of Significance and Pool Rules, 1953 December 29; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Preparation; Prechosen Sequences of Views, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, Paul A., and John W. Tukey
    - Present Nonuniqueness of Fiducial Inference, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Present State of Fiducial Probability, The, n.d.; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Prim-9: Pictorial Rotation and Isolation by Masking of point patterns presently in up to 9 dimensions, 1974; 6 items; Fisherkeller, Jerome H. Friedman, and John W. Tukey
    - Princeton Computer Problem - a Memorandum, The, 1 item; Buhler, Roald and John W. Tukey
    - Princeton's Program in Applied Analysis, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Principles of Sampling, 1954; 1 item; Cochran, William G., Frederick Mosteller, and John W. Tukey
    - Principles of Sampling, 1954 March; 2 items; Cochran, William G., Frederick Mosteller, and John W. Tukey
    - Probability Sampling Considerations, n.d.; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Problem about Normal Samples, 1954 March 16-17; 1 item; Arnold, Harvey J., Bradley D. Bucher, Hale F. Trotter, and John W. Tukey
    - Problem in Coincidence, 1942; 7 items; Tukey, John W
    - Problem in the Distribution of Rankings, A, 1949 September 28; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Problem of Berkson, A, 1948 October 25; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Problem of Berkson, and Minimum Variance Orderly Estimators, 1958; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Problem of Multiple Comparisons, The. (Comments on), 1952-1956; 9 items
    - Problem of Multiple Comparisons, The, 1973; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Problem of the Nile, The, 1949; 3 item; Tukey, John W
    - Problems of the Clinician Discussion, 1949; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Procedure for Calculating Values of Row and Column Badness for Two-way Tables and for Assessing the Relationship of Badness to Lambda, 1981; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Procedures for Dealing with Tetrapolarity, 1993 July 17; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Procedures for Separation with Batches of Values, III. The Case of Unequal Accuracy, 1988 May; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Procedures for Separations with Batches of Values, I. The Orderly Tool Kit and some Heuristics, 1988; 1 item; Hoang, Thu and John W. Tukey
    - Procedures for Separations within Batches of Values, II. More detailed Heuristics and some Simulation Results, 1988 December; 1 item; Hoang, Thu and John W. Tukey
    - Proceedings of the Workshop: Practical Application of the Frequency Approach to EEG Analysis, 1968; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Project Depth Gauge, n.d.; 1 item; Bogert, B. P., M. J. R. Healy, and J. W. Tukey
    - Projection Pursuit Algorith for Exploratory Data Analysis, A, 1974; 5 items; Friedman, Jerome H. and John W. Tukey
    - Proof of Contribution by Mulitple Regression: Traps and Opportunities, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Propagation of Errors, Fluctuations and Tolerances - Supplementary Formulas, 1958; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Propagation of Errors, Fluctuations and Tolerances, Basic General Formulas, 1957; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Properties - Lindelof, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Proposed "Bullet-proof" Analysis of Two-way Tables Whose Entries are Subject to Perturbations, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Proposed Procedure for Multigroup Fitting in the Two-coefficient Case, 1984 August 1; 4 items; Tukey, John W
    - Proposed Specifications for Computer Production of Tables, n.d.; 2 items; Gabbe, J. D. and John W. Tukey
    - Propugression Revisited, 1982 February 26; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Protecting Visibility in National Parks and Wilderness Areas, External Review Comments on, 1992; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Protecting Visibility in National Parks and Wilderness Areas, 1992 June 30; Folder 1; Committee on Haze in National Parks and Wilderness Areas: Source Apportionment and Control Options
    - Protecting Visibility in National Parks and Wilderness Areas, 1992 June 30; Folder 2; Committee on Haze in National Parks and Wilderness Areas: Source Apportionment and Control Options
    - Protecting Visibility in National Parks and Wilderness Areas, 1992 June 30; Folder 3; Committee on Haze in National Parks and Wilderness Areas: Source Apportionment and Control Options
    - Protocol for Key Statistical Analysis of the HEI CO-angina study, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Pseudo Standard Error for a Mode, 1972 February 28; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Pure and Hybrid Re-expression, 1992 January 13; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Purposes of Fiducial Inference, The, 1951; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Putting Reasonable Bounds on g's, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Quadrant Sum, Even Number in Sample, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Qualitative and Quantitative Confidence, 1988 October 31; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Quality Control Charts for Monitoring Instruments for Determining Laboratory Values (Using Successive Differences When Many are Zero), n.d.; 1 item; Ciminera, Joseph L. and John W. Tukey
    - Quantitative Vs. Qualitative Knowledge, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Quefrency Alanysis of Time Series for Echoes: Cepstrum, Pseudo-Autocovariance, Cross-Cepstrum and Saphe-Cracking, 1 item; Bogart, Bruce P., M. J. R. Healy, and John W. Tukey
    - Queries, n.d.; 1 item; Moore, Peter G. and John W. Tukey
    - Questionnaire Concerning the Annals, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Quick and Dirty Methods in Statistics. Part II - Simple Analyses for Standard Designs, 1951; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Quick and Easy Comparisons (1953 version), 1953 April; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Quick Plotting Routines for Teletypewriter-Like Terminals, 1971 November 12; 1 item; Andrews, D. F. and John W. Tukey
    - Quick, Compact, Two-sample Test to Duckworth's Specifications, A, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Randomization and Rerandomization: The Wave of the Past in the Future, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Randomization Methods for Tumor Sites with Few Tumor-Bearing Rodents, 1987 April; 1 item; Ciminera, Joseph, Joseph F. Heyse, Leonard Oppenheimer and John W. Tukey
    - Rational Interpolation Made Easy by a Recursize Algorithm, 1960; 2 items; Thacher, Henry C. and John W. Tukey
    - Re-Examination, from Statistical and Some Measurement View Points, of the Corrosion Measurements on the Widow's Creek No. 5 Boiler, A, 1977; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Re-Expression: A Direct Approach and its Consequences, 1989 March; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Re-Presentation of 2 Factor Interactions in a 2k, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Reading the Modified BNF of IWP 21 Aloud, 1968 February 5; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Receipe for Idiosyncratic Factorial Analysis, Using Levelling Techniques, A, 1980 October 23; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Recent Advances in Data Analysis, 1991; Folder 1; Bloomfield, Peter, Henry Braun and John W. Tukey